（ワスボガ）
ナメんな！侍女悪魔風情が！
Don't belittle me, you
puny Demon Maidservant!
（ヒルダ）ハッ！アーッ！ハッ！
ぐぉぉぁ～！
ターッ！
（ワスボガ）ぐわぁぁ～！
（姫川）≪おらぁ！そこまでだ！≫
Hey, that's far enough!
（神崎）てめえら　悪魔野学園の
奴らだな！
You're the bastards from
Akumano Academy, aren't you?
（姫川）人ん家で　えらく派手に
やってくれたじゃねえか。
Nice way to trash someone's
house, don't you think?
（東条）あっ　クマ！ってやつか？
They're one of those "Ah, Kuma!" guys, right?
（東条）決着をつけようぜ。
この前の奴は　どこだ？
Let's finish this...
Where's the bastard from before?
（寧々）悪魔野学園の奴らが
襲撃してきて！
The bastards from Akumano
Academy have come to attack!
（邦枝）そいつらと戦っちゃダメ！
私が行くまで→
You guys can't go fighting with
them! Wait until I arrive!
待ってるのよ！
（アンジェリカ）実は　父がこのお寺で
修業をしていたもので。→
You see, my father was
training at this temple...
わたくしも　そのお手伝いを。
And I have accompanied him.
同じ転送悪魔ってこと！？
今すぐ私を　転送して！
That means you're also a Dimensional
Transfer Demon, right?
Please, transfer me this instant!
（早乙女）いいか？悪魔の力を
人間が使う場合の→
Look, this is the form you use for
humans to utilize Demon's power.
図式は　こうだ。当然　悪魔と人間の
シンクロ度合いが→
Demon Power
Transform
And of course, the more in
sync the human and Demon are,
高ければ高いほど　引き出す
魔力も大きくなる。だが→
the more Demon power they can draw out.
But there is something you
need to be careful about.
ここでひとつ　気を付けねば
ならない事がある。
ん？
（早乙女）シンクロ度が上がると
いうことは　それだけ→
A higher synchronization rate means you're
getting closer to being a real Demon.
悪魔に近くなるということだ。
お前　紋章が全身に→
You had the mark cover your
entire body once, right?
現れたことが　あると言ったな？
（男鹿）ああ。
Yeah.
そりゃ　本当の危険信号だ。
悪魔化が進めば→
That's a major warning sign.
If you continue the Demon transformation,
you won't be able to go back to being human.
人間に戻れなくなってた
とこだぞ。→
俺が今から教える
紋章術ってのは→
The "Seal Technique" I'm going to teach you
is basically to prevent that from happening.
そうならない為の
術と言ってもいい。
（ベル坊）アダ。アダブダ
アダーダ。
（黒ベル坊）アダ…。
ニョダブダ。アィダブ…。
ダブダブ…。
ウダォ。ウィ…。
ニャ？
（早乙女）今　大事な話してるから。
Um, we're talking about
something important here.
向こう行って遊んでろ。
You two, go play over there.
アダブ！
ブダブダ！
ダブ…。
ブー。
しかし　えらいなついたな。
俺は　倒せっつったんだぞ。→
But man, you sure did befriend the
guy. I told you to defeat, remember?
一体　何したんだ　お前？
What the hell did you do?
いや…何って。
What did I do? Uh...
何か　あいつ　羽根とか尻尾が
急に生えたから　むしったら…。
Well, I thought after he suddenly
sprouted wings and a tail,
if I ignored him...
（早乙女）むしったの！？
You ignored him?
何か…こうなった。
And he got like this.
キー…ダブーダ！
I Am The Parent!
（焔王）どうしたのじゃ？
What's wrong?
（イザベラ）何でもありませんわ
坊っちゃま。
It's nothing, Master! Please,
continue with your game.
さっ　ゲームをお続けに。
（城山）ぐぉっ！
よっと！
（ファバス）テヤーッ！
ウッ！フッ！
ぐぉぉ～っ！
What the hell are these guys?
（夏目）こいつら　何者なの？
Move it! And check out my special move!
（神崎）どけ！俺の必殺技を
見せてやる！
ウッ！
フッ！
ウワッ…グワー。
前に　男鹿のヤローにやられてから
セラミック板の厚さ→
Ever since I was beat by Oga...
I doubled the thickness of my ceramic plate!
倍にしてんだよ！ターッ！
（姫川）アタタタ…。
…で　これの出力は３倍だ。
And I tripled this guy's output.
ウッ！
ウワッ！
こちとら　クマと素手でやりあって修業したんだ～！！
I trained by fighting bears bare-handed!
（ファバス）ウッ…。
（古市）本当にクマと？
（ラミア）バカなの！？→
With real bears?
Is he an idiot?!
Are all these people idiots?!
こいつら　みんなバカなの？
ウー…。
あん時のヤツは　どこだ？
出てきやがれ！
Where is that bastard from
before? Get 'im out here!
勝負は　まだついてねえ！
もう一度やらせろぉぉ～！！
Our fight ain't over yet!
Let me fight him again!
フフッ…人間だと思って
甘く見すぎていたようねえ。
It seems like we underestimated
you, since you were humans...
殺しても　かまわないわ。
やってしまいなさい！！
I don't mind if you kill them!
Now do it!
≪オッ！≫
≪ぐぉ～！≫
おもしれえ…。
Interesting...
こ　ここは危険だ！
It's dangerous here!
待ちなさいよっ！
Wait up!
ハァハァ…。
（チャイム）
ん？
Angelica-san?
アンジェリカさん！
（邦枝）≪待たせたわね≫
Looks like I'm a little late.
（古市）え～っ！
Leave this to me.
ここは　私に任せて。
うわぁ～！
Seems there's a strong-looking
opponent out here, too.
こっちにも　手ごたえ
ありそうなのが　いるじゃない。
フフッ…。
ヒルダ　てめえは引っ込んでろ。
Hilda, stand back.
あとは　俺に譲ってもらうぜ。
Let me handle the rest.
フン…。
Hilda-san, Oga!
ヒルダさん！男鹿！？
Alaindelon's actin' like a weapon!
アランドロン
武器みたいになっとる！
あ　古市じゃねえか。
Oh, Furuichi!
何してんだ　こんなとこで。
What are you doing up here?
何してんだじゃねえよ！
お前がいない間→
What am I doing, you ask?!
I've had it seriously rough
while you've been gone!
こっちは大変だったんだぞ！
つ～か　何だそりゃ！
And what the hell's with that? What
kind of training did you do, exactly?
一体　どんな修業してきたんだよ！
あ？何って　悪魔の力の使い方
教わってきたんだよ。
Huh? What kind?
I was taught how to use Demon power.
そ～ゆ～使い方？
悪魔　木刀？
Use it like that? A Demon as a wooden sword?
You needn't worry, Furuichi-dono.
（アランドロン）心配めさるな　古市殿。→
私からお願いしたのです。
何か力になりたいと。
It was I who requested it. I
wished to be of some help...
それに体は許しても
心までは…。
And even if my body is
no more, my heart will...
いくぜっ！魔剣アランドロン！
Here I go! Demon Sword Alaindelon!
い　痛い…。
It hurts!
あ～　あっ…。
千秋　あんたはそのまま
ゲームを続けてて。
Chiaki, keep playing the game.
（２人）あっ！
姐さん！
（邦枝）下がって。
Madame!
Get back.
（２人）うわ～！
Right!
Shingetsuryuu Sword School, Second Style...
Demon Clad Countless Petals
Scattering Sakura Blossoms!
ハァーツ！
てめえ　よくも
アランドロンを！
How dare you do that to Alaindelon!
（グラフェル）くだらん。茶番だな。
失せろ。→
This farce is stupid.
Get lost. I have no business
with you anymore.
もはや貴様には用はない。
あ？
貴様程度　いつでも
殺せると言ってるのだ。
I told you before, I can kill
someone like you whenever I want.
まずは侍女悪魔からだ。
I'll start with the Demon Maidservant.
これで借りは返したわ。
Now I've paid you back.
来たのか。
You've come?
ヘカドス！人の獲物に
手ぇ出してんじゃねえ！
Hecadoth, don't lay a hand on my prey!
待て待て。テメーの相手は俺だ。
Hold it. I'll be the one who fights you.
この前の決着
つけにきてやったぜ！
I've come to finish what we started before!
マー！！マーママママ…。
落ち着け　ベル坊。
ヒルダ　東条も邦枝も→
Calm down, Baby Beel.
Hilda. You too, Tojo, Kunieda.
悪いが　下がっててくれ。こいつは
俺たちだけで　やりてえんだ。
Sorry to say, but stand back. Everyone.
I'll fight them all myself.
ふざけんな　テメー。自分だけ
楽しもうってのか？
Screw you! Tryin' to hog
all the fun for yourself?
俺にも　やらせろ！
Let me mix it up!
頼むわ東条。
ダー。
Please, I gotta do this Tojo.
《坊っちゃま　いつの間にか
たくましい表情になられた…》
Master... He's suddenly
looking so gallant and brave.
わ～ったよ。今回だけは
貸しにしといてやる。
Fine, I get it. But just this once.
You owe me one. Next time, let me fight!
次は　ぜってえやらせろ！
とやっ！
フッ…よかろう。完膚なきまでに
叩きのめすがよい。
As you wish. Give them
all a thorough pounding.
ちょっと…。
おう。
ダッ！
Yup!
バカが。
Idiot...
一瞬で終わらせてやるよ。
その目障りな三文芝居。
I'll end this crappy little
play in an instant!
悪いけどよぉ　今回
てめえのターンは　なしだ。
Sorry to say, but you don't
get a turn this time.
な…何だ？
What?
（ナーガ）あれは　以前あの
スペルマスターが使った技。
That's...
That's the technique that
Spell Master used before.
そいつは目印だ。
That thing marks the spot.
今から　そこに　しこたま
ぶち込んでやるためのな！！
The spot I'm gonna punch
like there's no tomorrow!
なっ…何を？
What are you...
らぁぁぁぁ～！！
まだだよ。おぉぉぉ…
らぁぁぁ！
I'm not done yet!
必殺技　ゼブルエンブレム。
Special Technique: Zebel Emblem.
＜説明しよう！ゼブルエンブレム
とは　殴りたい人に→
Let me explain!
The Zebel Emblem is a technique
where you place the Zebel Spell
on someone you want to punch,
ゼブルスペルを乗せ　ボッコボコに
殴ると　あら不思議　殴った分だけ→
and beat the crap out of them!
Plus, mysteriously, the more you punch
the bigger the explosion! Just splendid!
爆発力が増すという
とてもステキな技である＞
なっ…なんつ～恐ろしい。
How frightful!
《この短期間で　ここまで
坊っちゃまの力を→
It's impressive he is able to use the
Master's power this well in such a short time.
使いこなすとは…。やはり
この男　計り知れん》
This man truly defies judgment.
さあて　次はてめえだ。
Now then, you're next.
水竜王ナーガ。気をつけろ
奴は柱爵。他の２人→
The Water Dragon King Naga.
Be careful. He's a Pillar Master.
He's a whole other league than Hecadoth
and Graphel, Pillar Generals...
柱将のヘカドスやグラフェルとは
比べものにならん。
よう　てめえが３人の中で
一番偉いってことは　首謀者か？
Yo. If you're the bigshot of the
three, then are you the leader?
いや　貴様を殺すことは
柱師団全員の意志だ。→
No. Killing you is the will
of the entire Pillar Division.
ってことは　てめえをぶっ倒しても
また次の奴が来るってわけか。
Which means that when I beat you,
the next ones will come for me.
そうなるな。
大将をやるまで
終わらねえってことか。
Yes, that's right.
It's not going to end 'til I
beat the head honcho, then?
そういうことになる。
That's how it is.
俺を殺して　どうする？
What'll you do when you kill me?
ベルゼ様を連れ帰る。
I'll take Beelze-sama back with me.
連れ帰ってどうする？
どうもせん。→
And after that?
Nothing. Lord En will destroy humanity.
焔王様が人間を滅ぼす。
そうか。
そうだ。
That so?
Yes.
フン！ベル坊は人間を
滅ぼしたりしねえよ。
Baby Beel isn't going to destroy humanity.
フッ…。
何で分かるかって？
Do you know why?
俺が親だからだ。
Because I'm the parent!
アイ…。
俺がこいつに　そんな
しょうもねえ事はさせねえ。
I won't let him do something so stupid!
ウッ…てめえは
調子に乗りすぎだぁ～！！
You're getting way ahead of yourself!
ウッ！
大将に伝えとけ。→
Tell this to your boss. I don't care
so much what happens to humanity.
人類がどうとか　興味ねえけど
ケンカしてえなら相手してやる。
But if he wants a fight, I'll give it to him.
まとめて　かかってこいってな。
Tell him to bring it on!
ウー…決定だ。死ねぇ！
It's decided!
Now die!
オッ！
Move it, Graphel.
（ナーガ）代わろう　グラフェル。
その男　危険だ。今のうちに
摘んでおかねば。
This man is dangerous.
We must crush him now.
うう…。いくぜ　ベル坊。
Let's go, Baby Beel!
ブラックベル坊と一緒に
編み出したあの技。
We'll do the technique we figured out
when we fought with Black Baby Beel.
スーパーミルクタイムだ！
It's Super Milk Time!
ダーッ！
ああ！
哺乳瓶！？
A milk bottle?!
スーパーミルクタイムだと！？
Did you just say Super Milk Time?!
（早乙女）あ～…。
Man...
やれやれ…男鹿の奴　とんでもねえ技　編み出しやがって。
That Oga came up with a crazy technique...
まさかオレが止めるだけで
こんなになっちまうとは。
Can't believe I got so
beat up just stopping him.
But it's best to only use
that thing once, Oga.
だがな…そいつを使っていいのは一度だけだぞ　男鹿。
ん…。
う～ん。
（一同）ああ…。
うう…！
Are we done yet?!
まだか！
まだだ！
Not yet!
I have to wait for it to cool to room
temperature! What'll I do if it burns?!
人肌になるまで冷まさね～と！
ヤケドしたら　どうすんだ！
相手のペースに飲まれるな
グラフェル。貴様の悪い癖だ。
Don't get swept up into your
opponent's pace, Graphel.
It's a bad habit of yours.
けどよ　ナーガ！
へっ　悪いな。
But, Naga...
Sorry, but it's almost ready...
そろそろ　いい感じだ。
ダーブ！
Oga... Somehow you've really
grown as a parent...
男鹿…なんだかんだで
親らしくなってきたなあ　マジで。
んぐんぐ…。
って　お前が飲むのかよ！
What? You're the one drinking it?!
アーダ！アーダ！
ゲッ！まずっ　ベル坊くん！
ダメだ！もうこれ以上は！
Ew!
Baby Beel-kun, please... No more!
ブーッ！
吐く！
I'm gonna puke! I'm gonna puke so, please!
吐くからカンベンして下さい！
What in the world is this?
なんなの？いったい…。
これは…まさか！
This... It couldn't be...
う～…きたきた～。
Here it comes...
魔力の絶対量が上がっていく…。
His maximum Demon power is rising...
まさか…無理矢理リミッターを
外しているのか！？
Could he have forcibly removed the limiter?
フッ　オレが
たっぷり吐かせてやるぜ！
I'll make you puke it all out!
（グラフェル・ヒルダ）ハッ！
あ～ダブダー。
男鹿？
Oga?
ダー…。
ダァ！
ダア！
ダッ！
あっ！
ダーッ！
なんて戦い方だ！
What kind of fighting is that?
It's crazy and wild... Like a child!
無茶苦茶で奔放…
まるで子供のような。
ブヒヒヒヒ！
ああ！
アーダダダダダッ！
Oga's become...
今の男鹿は…。
アタ～！
...Master Beelze himself!
ベルゼ坊っちゃま　そのもの…！
It's not just that he's strong...
強いなんてもんじゃない。
Baby Beel himself? What
do you mean, Hilda-san?
ベル坊そのものって！
どういうことですか！？ヒルダさん。
おそらく　あのミルクが
坊っちゃまと男鹿の境界を→
Perhaps that milk has broken down the
boundary between Oga and the Master!
あいまいにしているのだ。
境界！？
Boundary?
They've been in sync before
this at some percentage...
今まで何度かシンクロしたことは
あったが　これはその比ではない。
But this is incomparable to that!
今の男鹿は無尽蔵にあふれる
坊っちゃまの力を→
Right now Oga can pull out the unlimited
power flowing from the Master's body at will!
ほぼ　そのまま引き出せる…！
It is indeed the Great
Feast of the Demon Lord...
まさに魔王の大晩餐会
スーパーミルクタイム！
Super Milk Time!
だが　これは！
But, this is...
((もって５分。それ以上　使えば
お前は人間に→
You've got five minutes.
After that, not only will you
not be able to become human
戻れなくなるどころか
肉体が崩壊する))
your body itself will crumble.
And don't use it more than once at a time.
((くれぐれも連用はするな))
((って　おい　聞いてんのか！？))((へ～へ～))
Hey, are you listening?
Sure, yeah.
Interesting...
面白い。
ウィー？
フッ！
ダー！ダー！
アイーアイッ！
ダー！アダ！
アイ！
ダヒ。
にょ！
Water Ash Flow...
水燼濁々。
Snake Dragon Palm!
蛇竜掌！
ギャー！
男鹿！
（一同）ハッ！
Oga!
ハァハァ…。
ニョーン。
んぐんぐ…。
まだ上がるのか。
Again?
It's rising further?
いかん　男鹿！それ以上は！
You can't, Oga! Any more and...
んぐんぐ。
げぇぷ。
（男鹿ベル）ゲブー。
（一同）あ…あ…。
あれは…！
That's...
The Lord of the Flies' wings?
Could they have fused?
蠅王の翼。まさか融合して
いるのか？
（男鹿ベル）ウィー！
うっ！
この魔力！間違いない！
That Demon power... There's no mistaking it...
That's Beelze-sama borrowing a human body!
あれはもう人間の姿を借りたベルゼ様。
アイ！
アアアイーアイアイ。
アイアイー。
アイアイ　アアアイ…。
ベ…ベル坊？
Baby Beel?
Yes. He's become the Master, completely.
うむ…完全に坊っちゃまに
なっておるな。
Kinda, like, ew.
なんかヤダ…。
にょ。
なっ！
ああ！
アーウ。ダビ！ダブ！にょ～。
ズボンを脱ごうとしておられる！いけません！坊っちゃまぁぁ！
He's trying to take off his pants!
You mustn't, Master!
あ～危ない！やめてぇぇ！
いやあああ！
P-Please stop!
なんという丸出しへのこだわり！
Letting it all hang out
is so important to you?
ダッ！
That's far enough, Human!
そこ…までだ…人間！
Nice, Gill-Dude!
ナーイス！エラの人！
Yes!
うむ！
まだ生きてたのね！
I see you're still alive!
Oh, no!
オーノー！
にょ！？
とどめを刺さなかったのは間違いだったな　人間！
You made a big mistake not
finishing me off, Human.
ダブ？
今だやれ！ナーガ！
Do it now, Naga!
人間の身体さえ壊せば
ベルゼ様は戻れるはずだ！
As long as we defeat this human body,
Beelze-sama should return to normal!
Good job, you two.
よくやった　２人とも。
これで最後だ！
I'll end it with this!
Graphel! You'll die as well!
グラフェル！てめえも死ぬぞ！
へっ　こいつをやれるなら
それも本望。
If it gets rid of this
guy, that's all I ask for.
うっ！
こいつ…！
アー。
He's...
逃げろ！巻き込まれるぞ！
Run! We're going to be caught up in it!
（古市）え！？
（男鹿ベル）にょ！
（爆発音）
来た～！来たぞ！サテュラ！
Here it comes! Here it comes, Satura!
I've finally torn off the King Bimbo!
ついにキングビンボーを
引きはがしてくれたわ！
ここから余がドーンと！
From now on, I'm gonna explode on the scene!
（ドーン！）
（一同）キャー！
（爆発音）
うへ！ゴホゴホ！
大丈夫ですか？坊っちゃま。
Are you unharmed, Master?
（サテュラ）あいつら！なんちゅ～
無茶な戦いを。
What kind of insane battle are they having?
Who?! Who interrupted my game?!
誰じゃああ！余のゲームの邪魔を
してくれたのは！
I finally tear off the King Bimbo and now...
せっかくキングビンボーが離れてここから…！
（サテュラ・焔王・イザベラ）あ！
（由加・千秋・寧々）え。
（姫川・神崎）うう…あ…！
あ…あああ…あ。
う…うう…。
グーグー。
《力を使い果して元に戻ったか》
He used up all his power, and
returned to normal, is it?
((ベル坊は人間を滅ぼしたり
しね～よ))
Baby Beel isn't going to destroy humanity.
Because I'm the parent!
((オレが親だからだ！))
フッ…。
うう…ったく…男鹿のヤロー
無茶なことしやがって。
Damn you, Oga...
That was just nuts...
（ラミア）
ちょっと…重いんですけど！
Um... You're kinda heavy...
あ？
うわ～！違う違う！
断じて違う！
No, no! This is not right! Not right!
Whatever, just get off me!
（ラミア）
いいから早く降りなさいよ！
ぎゃ～！どきなさい！ぎゃ～！ぎゃ～！
Move it!
古市とかいったのぅ。余の嫁を…！
Furuichi, was it? That's
my wife, you bastard!
（古市・ラミア）え？
全面戦争じゃあ！貴様だけは
必ず余の手で　ぶちころす！！
This means all-out war!
I am going to kill you, especially,
myself! Mark my words!
え！？
ええ～！！
This is a misunderstanding!
Totally a misunderstanding!
誤解っすよ！誤解！
やめて下さいよ！変な想像！
Please, stop imagining such weird things!
That's right! Furuichi was just
protecting me from the falling rubble!
そ　そうよ～古市は瓦礫から私をかばってくれただけなんだから。
（ヨルダ）フン！
貸しを作ったなんて
思わないことね。ヒルダ。
Don't think I owe you for this, Hilda.
（一同）ああ…。
よいか　古市　近いうちに
必ず全軍　率いて来るからの！
Listen up, Furuichi.
I'll return shortly, leading my entire army.
それまでラミアを
預かっててもらうぜ。
You can have Lamia until then.
《余…今　かっこいい》
Yeah, that was pretty damn cool right there.
Let us go, Lord En.
（イザベラ）参りましょう。焔王様。
（神崎）おいおい　全員　飛んだぞ。
≪うそお≫
Hey, whoa... They all jumped!
They disappeared!
（由加）どこにもいないッスよ。
（姫川）んなバカな。
That's nuts...
やれやれ…ひとまず　これで
一件落着というところか。
Sheesh... I suppose we've
settled things for now?
どこらへんが
一件落着なんっすかあ！
Settled things how, exactly?!
He just said he was going to bring
back his entire army to kill me?!
オレ　全軍　率いて　殺しに来るとか言われたんすけど！
It should be Oga, right? Why me?
男鹿でしょ？普通！なんでオレ？
ねえ　なんで！？
Tell me why!
かわいそうな貴之…。
Poor thing, Takayuki...
Why are you calling me by my first name?
なんで呼び捨て！どさくさに
まぎれて距離つめてんじゃねえ！
Don't get so close to me!
Man, somehow we won!
And wow, Super Milk Time
is an incredible technique!
And heading with that theme, next
time me and Baby Beel switch bodies!
Um, wait...
What's with this preview?
It doesn't look like your usual Beelzebub!
Oh, I forgot.
Next time is Beelzebub's New Year's
Special: Beelbeel Journey to the West!
What?! Beelbeel Journey to the West?!
Think of it like a hidden talent competition.